/*************************************************
**
** You're viewing a file in the SMAPI mod dump, which contains a copy of every open-source SMAPI mod
** for queries and analysis.
**
** This is *not* the original file, and not necessarily the latest version.
** Source repository: https://github.com/poohnhi/PoohCore
**
*************************************************/

{
    "Changes": [
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Abigail"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Abigail loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Abigail {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Mom Caroline, Dad Pierre
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Abigail loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Abigail 1 2 1, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Abigail {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                // Friends Sam, Sebastian
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{AbigailFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Abigail 1 2 2, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Abigail {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Caroline"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Caroline loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Caroline {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Husband Pierre, child Abigail
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Caroline loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Caroline 1 2 1, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Caroline {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                // Friends Jodi
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{CarolineFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Caroline 1 2 2, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Caroline {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Clint"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Clint loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Clint {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Friends maybe Lucikiel if installed after the introduction event (add later)
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{ClintFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Clint {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Demetrius"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Demetrius loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Demetrius {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Robin Maru
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Demetrius loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Demetrius {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                // Special: Sebastian doesn't in friends and family of Demetrius so he'll get special dialogue (add later)
                // "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                //     "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                //     "Weight": 10,
                //     "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                //     "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: Lucikiel, Lucikiel}} loved false none}}}}",
                //     "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                //     "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Demetrius 1 2 2"
                // }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Willy"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Willy loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Willy {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Special: maybe some custom npcs
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{WillyFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Willy {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Elliott"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Elliott loved false {{DoNotSuggestGiftElliott}}}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Elliott {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{ElliottFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Elliott 1 2 2, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Elliott {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Emily"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Emily loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Emily {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Haley
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Emily loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Emily 1 4 1, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Emily {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: {{EmilyFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Emily 1 4 2 3 4, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Emily {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Evelyn"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Evelyn loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Evelyn {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // George Alex
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Evelyn loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Evelyn {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["George"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:George loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current George {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Evelyn Alex
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:George loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current George {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Gus"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Gus loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Gus {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // vanilla friends: Emily Pam
                // "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                //     "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                //     "Weight": 10,
                //     "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                //     "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Gus loved true none}}}}",
                //     "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                //     "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Gus {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                // }
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{GusFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Gus {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Haley"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Haley loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Haley {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Emily
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Haley loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Haley 1 2 1, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Haley {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                // Alex
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: {{HaleyFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Haley 1 2 2, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Haley {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Harvey"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Harvey loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Harvey {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Maru
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{HarveyFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Harvey {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
                // Harvey doesn't have relative
                // "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                //     "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                //     "Weight": 10,
                //     "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                //     "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Harvey loved true none}}}}",
                //     "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                // }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Jas"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Jas loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Jas {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Vincent only - maybe add special case for Shane and Marnie?
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Jas loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Jas {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Jodi"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Jodi loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Jodi {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Sam Vincent Kent
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Jodi loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Jodi 1 2 1, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Jodi {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                // Caroline
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{JodiFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Jodi 1 2 2, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Jodi {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Alex"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Alex loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Alex {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // George, Evelyn
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Alex loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Alex 1 4 1 2 3, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Alex {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                // Haley
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{AlexFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Alex 1 4 4, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Alex {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Kent"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Kent loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Kent {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Jodi Sam Vincent
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Kent loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Kent {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Leah"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Leah loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Leah {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Elliott
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{LeahFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Leah {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Lewis"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Lewis loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Lewis {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Marnie
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Lewis loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Lewis {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Linus"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Linus loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Linus {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{LinusFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Linus {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        // Marlon
        // Marnie
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Marnie"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Marnie loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Marnie {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Lewis, Shane, Jas
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Marnie loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Marnie {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Maru"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Maru loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Maru {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Maru loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Maru 1 5 1 2 3, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Maru {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: {{MaruFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Maru 1 5 4 5, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Maru {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Pam"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Pam loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Pam {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Penny, Gus
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Pam loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Pam {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Penny"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Penny loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Penny {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Pam
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Penny loved true 303-346-348-459-873}}}}", // Penny will never suggest item id that have one in these ids: 303-346-348-459-873
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Penny 1 5 1, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Penny {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{PennyFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Penny 1 5 2 3 4 5, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Penny {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Pierre"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Pierre loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Pierre {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Abigail, Caroline
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Pierre loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Pierre {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Robin"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Robin loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Robin {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Demetrius, Maru, Sebastian
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Robin loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Robin {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Sam"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Sam loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Sam {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Sam loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Sam 1 5 1 2 3, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Sam {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: {{SamFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Sam 1 5 4 5, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Sam {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Sebastian"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Sebastian loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Sebastian {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Robin Maru Sam
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Sebastian loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Sebastian {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Shane"],
            "Entries": {
                // Shane is one of special case. He'll be negative at 0 to 4 hearts, and positive at 5+ hearts
                "GiftTasteNegativePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteNegativePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonalNegative.{{Random:{{Range:1,3}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Shane loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Any Shane 0 4, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Shane {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Marnie
                "GiftTasteNegativeRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteNegativeRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelativeNegative.{{Random:{{Range:1,3}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Shane loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Any Shane 0 4, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Shane {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Shane loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Any Shane 5, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Shane {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Marnie
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Shane loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Any Shane 5, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Shane {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Vincent"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Vincent loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Vincent {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Jas
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Vincent loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Vincent {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Wizard"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Wizard loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{WizardFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Dwarf"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Dwarf loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Sandy"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Sandy loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Emily
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Sandy loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Krobus"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Krobus loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Maybe add Sen
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Leo"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Leo loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: {{LeoFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HAS_MAIL Host leoMoved"
                }
            }
        }
    ]
}